pamoja is a very traditional country
where the spirits of ancestors gods and
fortune-tellers are thought to be the
real custodians of well-being and
prosperity Cambodians prefer traditional
means of saving with little to no trust
in financial services Prudential
Insurance faced a difficult challenge to
introduce insurance as a means of
financial security in the minds of
Cambodians based on this popular can I
believe in faith the think insurance
campaign was born
the unground activation featured the
fortune teller spewed something
Cambodians love at the booth and also
made fortune-telling app disclose what
the head fate and heart lines have in
store for the user but ended with a
strong reminder a fortune teller only
points to a goal but insurance can
provide a way to get there so deceived
think life insurance KH com we also
handed out fortune cookies the amuse
guests were led consultation booths and
educated about insurance but that's not
all
on ground activation social media TV
radio and in the web all led to think
life insurance KH com
the nerve center of the campaign and
interacted for my website designed to
engage consumers and educate them in the
most basic terms of the importance of
insurance
Prudential did not push any products
into campaign its focus remained on
helping people understand the importance
of life insurance by acknowledging a
believe in fortune-telling credential
disable the ship Cambodians minds away
from passive acceptance instead of
leaving the future to faith
they took small but concrete steps to
proactively secure a brighter future
Prudential gave Cambodians proof that
even faith can be not in the right
direction
you